HINAH GHORI

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hinah-ghori-45915b113/

Cell No: 0335-2110432

Email: hinaghori5@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Masters of Business Administration Majors in Human Resources 2013 - 2016, KASBIT CGPA 3.0

EXPERTISE

- Talent Acquisition
- Performance Management
- Training & Development
- Payroll/ HR Policies
- Administration / Disciplinary Actions
- Conflict Management

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Microsoft Office: (Proficient in using Word, Excel Power Point and Outlook)
- ERP (MIS)
- Adobe Photoshop
- Dream Weaver

Career Profile

An Assistant Manager Human Resources with over 10 years of progressive experience in Human Resources and Business Administration in *Payroll Administration, Compensation/ Benefits, Performance Management, Recruitment and Selection, Training & Development, HR Policy and Organizational Design, People Management and Progress Improvement.*

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jagah Online.com SBDA - Project Sales

March 2022- Dec 2022

- Managed the business activities like closely working with current portfolio of customers and Induction of new potential customers.
- Managed to successfully achieve over and above targets assigned by the company and maintain AVR.
- Conclude business proposals, site office client's meetings, negotiations and closing deals.
- Provided impactful sales training and motivated sales team members to drive revenue growth.
- Analyze competitive product offerings in terms of features and benefits as well as price points.
- Managed high volume pipeline business & Tender business.
- Built deep relationships with Estate Agents & work on their inventory too

DANY TechnologiesAssistant Manager HR

Sep' 2021- March 2022

- Responsible for full life cycle of Recruitment process, from selecting, interviewing and
 Hiring candidates by using different social media channels LinkedIn, Facebook, WhatsApp Jobgroups,
 reputable Universities placement departments and Job fairs etc.
- Orientation of new joiners, Presentations of modified Policies, Trainings & developments as per Job requirements; CS, Sales, Organize the work place, work ethics etc.
- Prepare staff payroll including Tax, EOBI, Health Takaful, P.F, Loan, advances records etc.
- Prepare letters for appointment, confirmation, warning and termination.
- All operational activities on daily basis, attendance management, filing system, maintain data base regularly, SOPs, JDs, and Compliance of policies.

Achievement:

• Introduced the HR policies, and hired best candidates from the market for newly established business.

ArcPoint Solutions Pvt. Ltd - "IT Hardware Solutions Company"

Manager HR/ Admin - Sep' 2017 - Aug' 2021

Report to: CEO

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Address: House: R-37, Block'K' North Nazimabad. Karachi.

Nationality: Pakistani Languages: English / Urdu Marital Status: Single

- Responsible for full life cycle of Recruitment process, from selecting, interviewing and Hiring candidates by using different social media channels LinkedIn, Facebook, WhatsApp groups.
- Responsible for Employee Empowerment through development of KPI's and performance management system, Training & Development, Organization development and strategic plans effectively.
- Prepare letters for offer, appointment, confirmation, warning and termination.
- Compliance of Policies, dress code, leaves, filing system. Compliance for smooth attendance processin all branches of the company.
- Supervise and manage all day-to-day office administrative activities.
- Oversee facilities services, maintenance activities.

Achievement:

 Revised the leave policy according to the laws in vogue. Helped the management for planning the strategy for "work from home" during COVID Lockdown.

Javedan Corporation Ltd. (Arif Habib Group) 'Naya Nazimabad Project"

AM HR / Admin - Nov' 2015 - Aug' 2017Report

to: CEO/ Head of HR

- Prepare letters for offer, appointment, confirmation, warning and termination.
- Dealing in payroll, EOBI, Medical Gratuity all matters.
- Compliance of Policies, dress code, leaves, filing system. Compliance for smooth attendance process
- Handled employee's queries and grievances.
- Preparing the employees for assignments by establishing and conducting orientation.
- Organizing Employee Engagement Activities Picnic, Cricket tournaments, Annual Dinner etc.
- Completing human resources operational requirements by scheduling and assigning employees; following up on work results.
- All other HR & Admin related matters from time to time.
- Ensures provision of utility services in office like electricity, water, genet, Telephone, fax etc. and ensures continued supply without interruption.
- Maintains high standard of janitorial services in the office.
- Supervises kitchen functions and ensures its hygiene.
- Supervises drivers, peons, riders, telephone operator, sweeper etc. and ensures Efficiency on their part.
- Managing Kitchen Operations Ensure Hygiene Standards, Timely Serving of Food & Tea, Surprise Checking of Food Quality, Provision of Workers Uniforms

Achievement:

• Introduced the employee onboarding process enabling them to grasp the culture of the organization in a better way.

Generation's Pvt. Ltd – A Levels School

HR Officer - Oct' 2010 - Oct' 2015

Report to: Head of HR/ Manager HR

- Manage monthly disbursement of payroll, including expenses, incentives, medical reimbursements, festive pay, bonus, EOBI, SESSI, provident fund and taxes consistent with federal and state laws using ERP (Oracle).
- Timely processing of offer letters, appointment letters, confirmations, transfers, promotions, warning letters and terminations.
- Maintain Leave records of employees, prepare leave status reports at the end of every month and distribute to the Department Heads and employees.
- Induction program for the new recruits into the organization.
- Ensure compliance of policies, rules and regulations, assist in handling audit and compliance related matters, and assist in appraisals.

Personal traits and competence

- Excellent communication skills
- Team player & adaptable.
- Strategic & analytical problem solving skills.
- Negotiations & conflict resolution skills
- Establish work priorities and ability to strive under pressure
- Ability to communicate complex and highly sensitive information
- Ability to adhere to the strictest standards of confidentiality
- Highly motivated, keen learner and willing to take challenges